NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Legal Case File, 1915-1967 (Box 176-264)
  - Gray v. Main (elections, Ala.) (Box 203)
    - Background material
      - Voting and population records, Barbour, Bullock, Greene, and Macon counties, 1961-1966
        - Card files
          - Box 9 (Box 211)
          - Box 10 (Box 212)
          - Box 11 (Box 213)
          - Box 12 (Box 214)
        - County records
          - Photocopies See Oversize
          - Photographic film (Box 215)
            - 1 of 3
            - 2 of 3
            - 3 of 3
        - Notes and miscellany
          - 1 of 5
          - 2 of 5
          - 3 of 5
          - 4 of 5
          - 5 of 5 (Box 216)
    - Legal documents, 1967
      - 1 of 3
      - 2 of 3
      - 3 of 3
  - Gregg v. Sharpe, circa 1950 (education, D.C.)
  - In re Griffin v. City of Schenectady, 1950 (housing, N.Y.)
    - Correspondence and background material
    - Legal documents
  - Griffin v. Georgia, 1951 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - Groves v. Board of Educ. (education, Md.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1956-1958
    - Legal documents, 1958 (Box 217)
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
  - Guice v. Mayeaux, 1954 (criminal law, La.)
  - Guillory v. Saint Landry Parish School Bd., 1951 (education, La.)
  - Hale v. Tennessee, 1955 (criminal law, Tenn.)
  - Haley v. Ohio, 1948 (criminal law, Ohio)
  - Haley v. Sharpe, 1949 (education, D.C.)
  - Hall v. Roanoke-Chowan Hosp., 1965 (public accommodations, N.C.)
  - Hall v. United States, 1947 (criminal law, D.C.)
  - Hamilton v. Alabama, 1964 (criminal law, Ala.)
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Hampton v. Smith, 1950 (criminal law, Va.) See also Container 66, Martinsville Seven (Box 218)
  - Hampton v. Virginia, 1950 (Martinsville Seven) (criminal law, Va.)
  - Hardyman v. Collins, 1950 (criminal law, Calif.)
  - Harris v. Clinton (housing, Conn.)
    - Correspondence
      - 1951-1952
      - 1953-1957, undated
    - Background material, 1952-1953, undated
    - Legal documents
      - Central file, 1951-1955
      - General, 1951-1954, undated
    - Printed records, 1951-1954
  - Hart v. Knox County, 1948 (recreation, Tenn.) (Box 219)
  - Harvey v. Morgan, 1954 (labor, Tex.)
  - Hatfield v. Board of Supervisors, La. State Univ. (education, La.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1946-1947, undated
    - Legal documents, 1946-1947, undated
  - Hawkins v. Mississippi, 1955 (criminal law, Miss.)
  - Hayes v. County School Comm'n, 1959 (education, Tex.)
  - Heard v. Ouachita Parish School Bd., 1950-1951 (education, La.)
  - Henderson v. United States, 1950 (transportation, Md.)
  - Henry v. Board of Educ., 1955 (education, Kans.)
  - Henry v. Godsell, 1956 (education, Mich.)
  - Henry v. Rushton, 1955 (education, Kans.)
  - Henry v. Virginia, 1961-1963 (public accommodations, Va.)
  - Herndon v. Tallahassee Transit Co., 1957 (transportation, Fla.)
  - Heyward v. Public Hous. Admin., 1954-1956 (housing, Ga.)
  - Hickson v. Henry, 1952 (transportation, N.Y.)
  - Higgins v. Goodman, 1949 (education, Tex.)
  - Hill v. Hamtramck Hous. Comm'n. (housing, Mich.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1942-1947, undated
    - Legal documemts, general, 1942-1947, undated
    - Transcript, 1943
  - Hill v. International Bhd. of Boilermakers, 1955 (labor, R.I.)
  - Hill v. Texas, 1942 (criminal law, Tex.)
  - In re Hillburn School Dist. 15, 1931-1944 (education, N.Y.)
  - Hodge v. Tulsa County Election Bd., 1948 (elections, Okla.)
  - Holland v. Texas, 1948 (criminal law, Tex.)
  - Holmes v. City of Atlanta, 1955 (miscellaneous, Ga.)
  - Howard v. Lincoln Parish School Bd., undated (education, La.) (Box 220)
  - Howard v. Local 74, Wood, Wire, & Metal Lathers Int'l Union, 1954 (labor, Ill.)
  - Howard v. Saint Louis-San Francisco Ry., 1951 (labor, Mo.)
  - Huff v. Alabama, 1957 (criminal law, Ala.)
  - Hughes v. Lucky Stores, Inc., 1948 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Calif.)
  - Hundley v. Gorewitz, 1942 (housing, D.C.)
  - Hunt v. Arnold, 1956 (education, Ga.) See also Container 132, Georgia State College
  - Hunter v. City of New York, 1952 (housing, N.Y.)
  - Illinois v. Atkins, 1954 (criminal law, Ill.)
  - Illinois v. DeRose, 1951 (criminal law, Ill.)
  - Illinois v. Leighton, 1951 (housing, Ill.)
  - In re Ingram, 1953 (criminal law, N.C.)
  - Ingram v. Georgia, 1948 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - International Bhd. of Elec. Workers Local 35 v. Commission on Civil Rights, 1954 (labor, Conn.)
  - Iowa ex rel. Hooper v. Bennett, 1959-1960 (criminal law, Iowa)
  - Irvin v. Florida (criminal law, Fla.) See also Containers 52-54, Groveland, Fla.
    - Correspondence
      - 1949-1951
      - 1952-1953
      - 1954 (Box 221)
      - 1955-1956, undated
    - Background material
      - 1951-1952, undated
      - Undated
    - Legal documents, 1953
  - Irvin v. Florida (criminal law, Fla.) See also Containers 52-54, Groveland, Fla.
    - Related case, Florida v. Irvin, 1952
  - Ivey v. Texas, 1952 (criminal law, Tex.)
  - Ivory v. Edwards, 1951 (labor, N.Y.)
  - In re Jackson, 1955 (education, N.Y.)
  - Jackson v. Boger, 1950 (miscellaneous, Fla.)
  - Jackson v. McDonald; Lamar State College of Technology v. Jackson, 1956 (education, Tex.)
  - Jackson v. Seaboard Air Line Ry., 1947 (transportation, N.Y.)
  - Jackson Colored Teachers' Ass'n v. Callahan, 1944 (education, Tenn.)
  - In re Jacob, 1951 (miscellaneous, N.Y.)
  - Jamieson v. Louisiana State Bd. of Educ., 1965 (education, La.)
  - Jenkins v. Chicago Hous. Auth., 1953 (housing, Ill.)
  - Jennings v. Board of Trustees, 1947 (education, Tex.)
  - Johnson v. Alabama, 1964 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Ala.) (Box 222)
  - Johnson v. Board of Supervisors, 1946-1947 (education, La.)
  - Johnson v. Crawfis, 1954 (public accommodations, Ark.)
  - Johnson v. Illinois Cent. R.R., 1951 (transportation, Ill.)
  - Johnson v. Levitt & Sons, Inc. (housing, Pa.)
    - Correspondence
      - 1954
      - 1955-1960
    - Background material, 1955-1958
    - Legal documents, 1954-1955
  - Johnson v. Mississippi, 1954-1955 (criminal law, Miss.)
  - Jones v. Balkcom, 1953 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - Jones v. School Bd., 1960 (education, Va.)
  - Jones v. Southeastern Greyhound Lines, 1953 (public accommodations, Ala.; also transportation)
  - Joseph v. Boyce, 1955 (labor, N.Y.)
  - Kelley v. Board of Educ. (education, Tenn.) (Box 223)
    - Background material, 1955-1959
    - Legal documents
      - General file
        - 1955-1957
        - 1958-1959, undated
      - Transcripts
        - 1956
        - 1958
    - Printed records, 1959
  - Kelly v. School Bd., 1948 (education, Va.)
  - Kelsey v. Moore, 1946 (elections, Va.)
  - Kemp v. Rubin, 1946 (housing, N.Y.) (Box 224)
  - Kennard v. McKamer Realty Co., undated (housing, Md.)
  - Kennard v. Mississippi (criminal law, Miss.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1961-1963, undated
    - Legal documents
      - Central file, 1961-1963, undated
      - General, 1961-1963, undated
      - Transcripts, 1961
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
  - Kennedy v. State Budget & Control Bd., 1955 (education, S.C.)
  - Kennedy v. Tennessee, 1948 (criminal law, Tenn.)
  - Keys v. Carolina Coach Co. (transportation, N.C.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1952-1961
    - Legal documents, 1954-1955 (Box 225)
    - Related cases, 1954-1955, undated
      Campbell v. Greyhound Bus Lines
      Freeman v. Greyhound Bus Lines
      NAACP v. Saint Louis-San Francisco Ry.
      Walker v. Southeastern Greyhound Bus Lines
  - Korean War and World War II Court Martial Records, 1943-1952 See also Container 18, Korean trip; Container 43, Korean War; Container 99, Korea, defense fund; and Containers 152-154, Korea
    - *Alston, Nelson L., 1944, (3 folders)
    - *Anderson, Eugene W., 1950
    - *Arnold, John H., 1945
    - *Austin, Arthur, and Percy Brown, 1948
    - *Baker, Henry P., 1953
    - *Bennett, Herbert, 1950 (Box 226)
    - *Blaze, Herman, and Fred Cavitt, Jr., 1950
    - *Bledsoe, Roosevelt, 1950
    - *Bosley, Walter, Jr., 1952
    - *Bouchee, Willie L., 1950
    - *Brewer, Eddie, 1950
    - *Brown, Albert E., 1955
    - *Brown, Robert L., and Harold E. Hutchens, 1950
    - *Bryant, Carsin, 1950
    - Butler, Judge, 1950-1951
    - *Cail, Lee, 1953
    - *Cash, Clarence, 1950
    - *Clark, David, 1951
    - *Drummond, Harry B., 1950
    - *Dyson, Charles R., 1953
    - *Faulkner, Spencer F., 1956 (Box 227)
    - *Fortes, Anthony P., 1950
    - *Franklin, Glenn E., 1950
    - *Freeman, Columbus, Jr., and Thomas W. Butler, 1951
    - *Fulsom, Clarence E., 1950
    - *Glisson, John W., 1950
    - *Graves, David L., 1950
    - *Halsby, Everett M., 1951
    - *Harris, Harold O., 1951
    - *Hazzard, George, 1944
    - *Henderson, John H., 1952
    - *Howard, Nathaniel, and David J. Borner and Clifford E. Ware, 1951 (Box 228)
    - *Hunter, Fred, 1944
    - *Jackson, Otis W., 1955-1956
    - *James, Jesse, and Henry E. Carr and James C. Crawford, 1950
    - *Johnson, Edward W., 1952
    - *Johnson, Floyd, 1951
    - *Johnson, Marion, 1953
    - *Laws, Clarence A., 1949-1956
    - *Lester, Robert, 1955-1956
    - *Mann, Joseph A., and Albert R. Myers, 1953, (2 folders) (Box 229)
    - *Marshall, John E., and Clarence L. Shelton, 1951
    - *Martin, Jeffrey, and Eugene Lewis, 1950
    - *McCrawford, William, 1943
    - *McDonald, Louis G., 1952
    - *McMillan, William E., 1945
    - *Miller, Robert L., 1950
    - *Moore, Arrice C., 1945
    - *Moore, Henry, 1950
    - *Morgan, J.P., 1950
    - *Nelson, James A., 1951-1952
    - *Norris, Willie W., 1951
    - *Paulfrey, Peter J., Jr., 1950 (Box 230)
    - *Petross, Bruce H., 1951
    - *Pitts, Ezell, 1953
    - *Reed, Hobert, 1950
    - *Reed, Nathaniel, 1950
    - *Roberts, James Roy, 1950
    - *Royston, John E., 1952
    - *Simmons, Bennie P., and Allen Woods, Jr. and James E. Duffer, 1951
    - *Sturgis, Robert Lee, 1950
    - *Turner, Thomas L., 1956
    - *Waddell, Fred, 1950
    - *Walker, Tommie L., 1950
    - *Ware, Armeka, 1952
    - *White, Verlon S., 1950
    - *Whiteside, Charlie, 1950
    - *Williams, Ezell, 1950 (Box 231)
    - *Williams, Leonard J., 1959
    - *Williams, Luther, 1950
    - *Wilson, David C., and James A. Solomon and Ralph R. Young, 1945
    - *Woodson, George L., and Jessie Williams, 1951
  - Lancaster v. Hammond, 1949 (miscellaneous, Md.; "Ober Bill Case")
  - Lange v. Rancher, 1953 (public accommodations, Wis.)
  - Lark v. Louisiana Bd. of Educ., 1957 (education, La.)
  - Lassiter v. Northampton County Bd. of Elections, 1957 (elections, N.C.) See also Container 175, same heading
  - Law v. Mayor of Baltimore, 1948 (public accommodations, Md.)
  - Lawton v. Dewey, undated (armed forces, N.Y.)
  - Leakes v. Virginia, 1953 (criminal law, Va.) (Box 232)
  - LeBeauf v. State Bd. of Educ. (education, La.)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1965
    - Legal documents, 1965
  - Lee v. Board of Educ., 1943 (education, Mo.)
  - Leib v. O'Neal, 1954 (criminal law, La.)
  - Lesser v. Lesser, 1952 (miscellaneous, Wash.)
  - Lewis v. City of Detroit (housing, Mich.)
    - Correspondence
      - 1942-1949
      - 1950
      - 1951
      - 1952-1953
      - 1954-1955, undated
    - Background material, 1942-1955, undated (Box 233)
      - 1 of 4
      - 2 of 4
      - 3 of 4
      - 4 of 4
    - Legal documents
      - 1949-1955
      - Undated (Box 234)
    - Printed records, 1954, undated
  - Madison v. University of Mo. Medical School, 1950 (education, Mo.)
  - Malicke v. Milan, 1948 (housing, Mich.)
  - Manning v. Crowl, 1953 (public accommodations, Pa.)
  - In re Marshall, 1949 (miscellaneous, N.J.)
  - Maryland v. Askin, 1948 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Md.)
  - Mathews v. Orgill, 1958-1960 (public accommodations, Tenn.)
  - McCormick v. Green, undated (housing, Ill.)
  - McDaniel v. Board of Public Instruction, 1941 (education, Fla.)
  - McDuffie v. Florida Turnpike Auth., 1960-1961 (public accommodations, Fla.)
  - McKelpin v. Orleans Parish School Bd., 1941-1942 (education, La.)
  - McKissick v. Durham City Bd. of Educ. (education, N. C.)
    - Background material, 1957-1959
    - Legal documents, 1957-1959
  - McSwain v. County Bd. of Educ., 1950-1956 (education, Tenn.)
  - Meenan v. Meenan, 1954 (domestic relations, N.Y.)
  - Meredith v. Fair (education, Miss.)
    - Correspondence, 1962, undated
    - Background material (Box 235)
      - General file, 1961-1962
      - University of Mississippi, 1960-1962
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
    - Legal documents
      - Amicus curiae, United States, 1962
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Central file, 1961-1963
        - 1 of 6
        - 2 of 6 (Box 236)
        - 3 of 6
        - 4 of 6
        - 5 of 6
        - 6 of 6
        - Evidence, 1961-1962
        - General
          - 1 of 5
          - 2 of 5 (Box 237)
          - 3 of 5
          - 4 of 5
          - 5 of 5
      - Transcripts, 1961
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3 (Box 238)
        - 1962
    - Printed records, 1961-1963
      - 1 of 6
      - 2 of 6
      - 3 of 6
      - 4 of 6
      - 5 of 6 (Box 239)
      - 6 of 6
    - Related cases
      - Mississippi ex rel. Barnett v. Meredith, 1962
      - United States v. Barnett, 1963
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
  - Merrit v. Green Room, 1951 (public accommodations, Hawaii)
  - Middlebrooks v. City of Birmingham, 1964 (criminal law, Ala.)
  - In re Middlebrooks, undated (criminal law, Calif.)
  - Mid-Island Properties v. Johnson, 1953 (housing, N.Y.)
  - Miller v. McComb, 1954 (housing, N.J.)
  - Mills v. Lowndes, undated (education, Md.)
  - Ming v. Horgan, 1954-1957 (housing, Calif.)
  - Mississippi v. Johnson, 1954 (criminal law, Miss.) (Box 240)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Missouri v. School Dist., 1951 (education, Mo.)
  - Missouri ex rel. Brewton v. Board of Educ., 1949 (education, Mo.)
  - Missouri ex rel. Toliver v. Board of Educ., 1949 (education, Mo.)
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4 (Box 241)
  - Mitchell v. Connellee, 1955 (education, Md.)
  - Moorman v. Morgan, 1954 (public accommodations, Ky.)
  - Morris v. Greyhound Corp., 1954 (transportation, N.Y.)
  - Morris v. Housing Auth., 1954 (housing, Ala.)
  - Morris v. Williams, 1945 (education, Ark.)
  - Mosley v. Georgia, 1955 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - Mrsa v. Reynolds, 1946 (housing, Mich.)
  - Muir v. Louisville Park Theatrical Ass'n, 1953 (public accommodations, Ky.)
  - NAACP v. Saint Louis & San Francisco Ry., 1953 (transportation, N.Y.) See also Container 162, same heading
  - NAACP v. Texas, 1956-1960 (miscellaneous, Tex.) See also Containers 247-251, Texas v. NAACP
  - Namba v. McCourt, 1948 (housing, Oreg.)
  - Neal v. Graham, 1954 (criminal law, Utah)
  - Neville v. Orange County Bd. of Educ., 1961 (education, N.C.)
  - New Jersey v. Lewis; New Jersey v. Parker, 1948 (criminal law, N.J.)
  - New Negro Alliance v. Sanitary Grocery Co., 1938 (labor, D.C.)
  - Newman v. Searcy, 1949 (elections, Ala.)
  - New York ex rel. Bracey v. Salter, 1949 (criminal law, N.Y.)
  - New York v. Cornelius, 1955 (criminal law, N.Y.)
  - New York v. Kelly, undated (criminal law, N.Y.)
  - New York ex rel. Portnoy v. Strasser, 1951-1952 (miscellaneous, N.Y.)
  - Nichols v. McGee, 1957 (criminal law, Calif.)
  - North Carolina v. Jackson, 1954 (criminal law, N.C.) See also Container 161, same heading
  - North Carolina v. Simmons, 1951 (criminal law, N.C.) (Box 242)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - North Carolina v. Williams, 1960 (civil rights protest demonstrations, N.C.)
  - Northcross v. Board of Educ., undated (education, Tenn.)
  - Ocasio v. Fox, 1952 (labor, N.Y.)
  - Palmer v. Southern Ry., 1948 (labor, D.C.)
  - Payne v. Board of Supervisors of La. State Univ., 1951 (education, La.)
  - Pearson v. Olney Gardens, 1955 (housing, Pa.)
  - Pennsylvania ex rel. Hatton v. Dye, 1953 (criminal law, Pa.)
  - Pennsylvania ex rel. Johnson v. Thomas, 1944 (criminal law, Pa.)
  - Perry v. Cyphers, 1951 (elections, Tex.)
  - Phillips v. Naff, 1952 (housing, Mich.)
  - Phillips v. Phoenix Union High Schools, 1953 (education, Ariz.)
  - Plummer v. Casey, 1953 (public accommodations, Tex.)
  - Prater v. Tennessee Bd. of Educ., 1958 (education, Tenn.)
  - Reeves v. Alabama, 1953-1957 (criminal law, Ala.)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Register v. Sandefer, 1949 (recreation, Tex.)
  - Rice v. Sioux City Memorial Cemetery, 1953 (public accommodations, Iowa) (Box 243)
  - Roberts v. Seaboard Air Line Ry., 1944 (transportation, Va.)
  - Robinson v. Hunter, 1961 (public accommodations, Va.)
  - Robinson v. Mississippi, 1955 (criminal law, Miss.)
  - Rolax v. Atlantic Coast Line R.R., 1950 (labor, Va.)
  - Romero v. Weakley; Burleigh v. Weakley, 1955 (education, Calif.)
  - In re Rooks, 1952 (criminal law, Tex.)
  - Ross v. Rogers, 1957 (education, Tex.)
  - Scott v. Beard, 1954 (elections, La.)
  - Scruggs v. Loftin, 1952 (education, Tex.)
  - Scull v. Committee on Law Reform & Racial Activities, 1957 (criminal law, Va.)
  - Scurry v. Sukup, 1951 (recreation, N.J.)
  - Sealy v. Department of Pub. Instruction, 1957 (education, Pa.)
  - Seawell v. MacWithey, 1948 (housing, N.J.)
  - Shanks Village Residents Ass'n v. Cole, 1954 (housing, D.C.)
  - Shannon ex rel. Cox v. Board of Educ. of Nashville, 1954 (education, Tenn.) See also Container 109, same heading
  - Shelton v. Alabama, 1964 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Ala.)
  - Shepherd v. Florida (criminal law, Fla.) (Box 244)
    - Background material (petitions), 1951-1952
      - 1 of 7
      - 2 of 7
      - 3 of 7
      - 4 of 7
      - 5 of 7
      - 6 of 7
      - 7 of 7 (Box 245)
    - Legal documents, 1950-1951
  - Shields v. City of Chillicothe, 1955 (recreation, Mo.)
  - Simmons v. Edwards, 1960 (education, Tex.) See also Container 143, same heading
  - Simmons v. Ouachita Parish School Bd., 1954 (education, La.)
  - Simmons v. Wallace, undated (education, N.C.)
  - Sims v. Board of Pub. Instruction, 1950 (education, Fla.)
  - In re Skipwith, Rector (education, N.Y.)
    - Legal documents, 1958-1959
    - Printed records, 1958
  - Smith v. Alabama, 1963-1964 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Ala.)
  - Smith v. Baldwin, 1948 (elections, Ga.)
  - South v. Peters, 1950 (elections, Ga.)
  - South Carolina v. Bullock, 1959 (criminal law, S.C.)
  - South Carolina v. Harvey, 1951 (criminal law, S.C.)
  - Steiner v. Simmons; Simmons v. Steiner, 1954 (education, Del.) (Box 246)
  - Stephens v. Board of Graded School Trustees, 1948 (education, N.C.)
  - Stevens v. Hedgpeth, 1947-1948 (education, N.C.)
  - Stevenson v. Harris, 1948 (education, Tex.)
  - Stewart v. Clark Terrace Unit One, Inc. (housing, La.)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1955
    - Background material, 1952-1954, undated
    - Legal documents, 1954, undated
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
  - Stewart v. Lincoln-Douglas Hotel Corp., 1952 (public accommodations, Ill.)
  - Swanson v. University of Va., 1950 (education, Va.) (Box 247)
  - Syres v. Oil Workers Union Local 23, 1955 (labor, Tex.)
  - Tate v. City of Eufaula, undated (housing, Ala.)
  - Taylor v. Blandford, 1945 (housing, D.C.)
  - Taylor v. Board of Educ., 1955 (education, W.Va.)
  - Taylor v. Board of Educ., 1956-1961 (education, N.Y.)
  - Taylor v. Brotherhood of Ry. & S.S. Clerks, 1951-1952 (labor, D.C.)
  - Taylor v. Leonard, 1954 (housing, N.J.)
  - Taylor v. Seaboard Air Line R.R., 1953 (transportation, Fla.)
  - Tennessee v. Pillow, 1946 (criminal law, Tenn.)
  - Texas v. NAACP (miscellaneous, Tex.) See also Container 241, NAACP v. Texas
    - Legal documents
      - General file, 1956
      - Exhibits, 1956
        - Vol. I
        - Vol. II (Box 248)
        - Vol. III
        - Vol. IV
        - Vol. V
        - Vol. VI
        - Vol. VII, 1 of 2 (Box 249)
        - Vol. VII, 2 of 2
        - Vol. VIII
        - Vol. IX
        - Vol. X
        - Vol. XI
      - Oral testimony, 1956 (Box 250)
        - Vol. II
        - Vol. III, 1 of 2
        - Vol. III, 2 of 2
        - Vol. III, supplement, 1 of 2
        - Vol. III, supplement, 2 of 2
        - Vol. IV
        - Vol. IV, first supplement (Box 251)
        - Vol. IV, second supplement
        - Vol. V
        - Vol. VII
  - Thomas v. City of Birmingham, 1963 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Ala.)
  - Thomas v. Gray, 1951 (education, N.C)
  - Thomas v. Hibbitts, 1942 (education, Tenn.)
  - Thomas v. Mississippi (civil right protest demonstrations, Miss.; "Mississippi Freedom Riders") (Box 252)
    - Background material, 1961-1964, undated
    - Legal documents
      - General file, 1962-1964, undated
      - Transcripts, 1962
        - 1 of 4
        - 2 of 4
        - 3 of 4
        - 4 of 4
    - Printed cases
    - Related cases (Box 253)
      - Ackerberg v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Adler v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Aelony v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Anderson v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Armstrong v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Baer v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Bell v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Bennett v. Mississippi, 1963 (Box 254)
      - Berman v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Bevel v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Blevins v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Blue v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Bromberg v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Clarke v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Copeland v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Davidov v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Davis v. Mississippi, 1962
      - De Russ v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Denson v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Donald v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Eisenberg v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Farmer v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Feingold v. Mississippi, 1962 (Box 255)
      - Filner v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Floyd v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Frieze v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Fuller v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Gerbac v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Givens v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Green, M. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Green, R. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Griffin v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Grubbs v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Hanson v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Harbour v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Heller v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Herrick v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Hirshfeld v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Horne v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Jackson v. Mississippi, 1963 (Box 256)
      - Kaufman v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Knight v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Leons v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Manning v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Martinson v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Matzkin v. Mississippi, 1962
      - McConnell v. Mississippi, 1961
      - McDonald v. Mississippi, 1962
      - McDonald v. Mississippi, 1965
      - McKinnie v. Mississippi, 1962
      - McNair v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Miller v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Mitaritonna v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Morton v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Palmer v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Patton v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Pavesic v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Perkins v. Mississippi, 1963 (Box 257)
      - Perlman v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Pestana v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Peterson v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Petway v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Phillips v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Pleune, J. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Pleune, K. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Posner v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Price v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Prichard v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Randolph v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Reed v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Richards v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Rogers v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Roland v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Rosell v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Rosenbaum v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Rosenberg v. Mississippi, 1962 (Box 258)
      - Rosett v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Ross v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Schwarzchild v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Seller v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Sheviakov v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Siegel v. Mississippi, 1962